This course will teach you React
from the ground up and in great detail.
But this course section here
will actually not be about React,
but instead about just JavaScript.
It will allow you to refresh your JavaScript knowledge
and therefore, this course section here is optional.
You can therefore skip it,
and you can of course also always come back to it
if later in the course
you see that you need some extra JavaScript help
because this course section here
is recommended if you haven't used JavaScript in a while
or if you don't have a lot of JavaScript experience.
But I'll also say right away,
that this section does not replace a JavaScript course.
This section is not for you
if you have absolutely no JavaScript experience
because if that's the case,
you should definitely at least
explore some JavaScript basics
before continuing with this course.
But this section here,
will revisit crucial JavaScript concepts
and it will especially take a closer look at
the core JavaScript concepts you need
for building React apps,
so for writing React code, you could say
because in this section here
we will revisit the core JavaScript
syntax and rules you should follow
when writing JavaScript code.
We'll explore the essential modern JavaScript
features you should know in general,
and will, of course also, especially focus on the features
you need to write React code.
So the features you will use throughout this course,
that's what you'll get out of this section.