So, let's dive right in.
And for that, I prepared a CodeSandbox project,
a CodeSandbox environment,
to which you, of course,
find a link attached to this lecture,
which gives you a very basic web project
with an HTML file and some assets.
No JavaScript code yet, though.
And this is the project we'll use for playing around
with JavaScript and for exploring some basic features.
I will also say, right away,
that we'll mostly write code
that will output content in the console,
which in CodeSandbox can be accessed
by clicking on "Console" here.
Because this section
is not about building some super fancy,
JavaScript-based project.
Instead, as mentioned,
it is about refreshing your JavaScript knowledge
and making sure that you have all the essentials you need
for building React apps.