So let's start
by revisiting certain crucial core concepts
and things you should know about JavaScript,
for example, that JavaScript can be executed
in many different environments.
For example, of course, the browser,
that's where JavaScript originated.
In the end, that's what it was built for
back in the nineties.
But nowadays, thanks to NodeJS and Deno,
for example, you can also execute JavaScript code
outside of the browser.
This will not be the focus of this course
because this is a React course
and React is a client-side, front-end,
browser-based library in its core
that allows you to build user interfaces
with React and JavaScript.
But it is of course worth knowing
that JavaScript is not limited to the browser.
You can even build mobile apps with JavaScript,
thanks to extra technologies
like Capacitor or React Native,
which by the way,
would be a great next step
after finishing this course.
You can also use React
in conjunction with another tool
or another library you could say,
called React Native,
to build native mobile apps
for Android and iOS.
And I do have
a dedicated course on React Native
if you wanna learn more about that
after finishing this course.
So JavaScript is really versatile, really powerful.
But in this refresher section,
we are going to focus
on JavaScript in the browser,
though the general syntax
and rules of course,
are always the same,
no matter for which environment
you are writing your JavaScript code.
So since we focus on JavaScript in the browser,
let's explore how JavaScript code
can be added to a website.
And here you have two main options
and they both include the special script tag,
the special script element,
which you can add to your HTML code.
You can either put your JavaScript code
between such script tags,
or you can use those script tags
to import JavaScript files,
which then contain your JavaScript code.
Now typically,
we don't use that inline approach
on the left here,
where the code is between those script tags,
because this approach
can quickly lead to unmaintainable
and complex HTML files,
and is therefore typically
only used for very short scripts.
Instead, typically,
you have your JavaScript code
in dedicated JavaScript files
because such projects that use this approach
are way easier to maintain.
Therefore, here in this demo project
which I prepared,
we could start in this assets folder
by adding a new sub-folder
that could be called scripts,
though the name of course doesn't matter.
And in there,
we can create a JavaScript code file
that could be named app.js.
Though this name also is totally up to you,
it just should end with .js,
so instead of course tells the browser
and also the Code Editor
that this file will contain JavaScript code.
And the Code Editor can therefore,
for example, make sure that the code
is properly highlighted and formatted.
Well, and with such a file added here,
you can then import it in the HTML file
by going there
and adding your script tags,
opening and closing script tags.
And you always need both.
You can't use a self-closing script tag
or anything like this.
Instead, you need opening
and closing script tags.
That's a must have.
Now you can add them
anywhere you want in that file.
In the head section,
in the body section,
really, anywhere you want.
And then you would add the source attribute,
the src attribute
to point at the file.
In my case, in the assets folder.
And there in the scripts folder
that should be imported.
And now that file would be loaded
as part of this webpage
when the webpage is loaded.
Now it is worth noting that
you can then add extra attributes
to the script tag.
For example, the defer attribute,
to make sure that the script
that will be imported,
will only be executed
after the rest of the HTML document
has been read and parsed.
This ensures that,
if your script code,
for example, needs to work
with some HTML elements,
those HTML elements are available
when the JavaScript code starts executing.
Without defer,
it would start executing right away.
And if you then would try
to reach out to this unordered list,
for example, this unordered list
might not be available yet
if the script is loaded
before the list is output here.
That's why you might want to add defer.
Now in modern JavaScript projects,
it's also quite common
that you have another attribute
on your script tags
instead of having defer.
And that would be the type attribute,
which then is set to module like this.
Now, this type module attribute
here on the script tag makes sure
that this JavaScript file
is treated as a JavaScript module.
And if you are treating
your JavaScript files as modules,
this unlocks one very important new syntax.
The import syntax,
where you can import code
from script A into script B.
For example, here we could have
a second script file,
util.js,
which might contain some utility functionality.
And in that script file,
we could export something
with the export keyword,
and then import it
in the app.js file.
Now we'll explore this import export syntax
and this general module feature
in greater detail soon.
But before we get there,
there's one other super important thing
you should know about the script tag
here in the HTML file.
Because before we get there,
there is one other super important thing
you should know about these script tags
and about importing script files
in the context of building React apps.
Because when you're working
on a React project,
you will almost never add these script tags
to your HTML file on your own,
because React projects almost
always use a build process
which as part of that build process,
injects these script tags
into the HTML code for you.
And then the next lecture will explore
why we use such a build process
in React projects.