So, now that we got started
with components and props,
and how we can build basic React applications,
it's time to practice what we learned,
and it's of course specifically time
to practice working with those components,
because as you learned,
components are a crucial React concept,
and the core building block of all those user interfaces
you are going to build with React.
Therefore, in this course section here,
we're going to build this demo application,
this very basic website
which will utilize this component concept,
or which code will utilize this component concept,
and the idea behind this section here
is that you can practice what you learned.
For that, in this section,
you're going to split an existing component,
an existing React application, you could say,
into smaller components,
and you're therefore going to create
and use multiple custom components,
and you are also going to need to pass data
to some of those components.
So, that's also something you're going to do
in this course section.
In the next lecture, I'll provide you
with a starting project and your main tasks,
and thereafter,
you should try to complete those tasks on your own.