So let's now take a look at our code
and identify possible components into which we could
split up the current code.
For that, if you take a look at the current code,
the current JSX code, to be precise,
I got at least two components
into which this could be split up.
And that would be the header component,
that could be a separate component.
And then one reusable component for those key concepts.
So this list item could go into its own reusable component.
We could also build a third component,
this concept component, but that is optional.
You could definitely do it though, I will say that.
Now, before we go ahead and build those components,
I wanna briefly explain why we could split the app
into those components I just mentioned.
And for that, I first of all want to say that of course
for a very simple website like this one here,
leaving the code like this wouldn't be wrong,
wouldn't be horrible.
But of course this is just a basic demo absence,
we're just getting started with React.
And of course we wanna practice those key React
concepts you already learned about,
like components for example.
And there actually also is a good reason for
splitting this up into components.
At least a separate component for these concepts
makes a lot of sense, because right now,
if I ever decide that I wanna get rid of this
description paragraph, for example,
I have to delete this paragraph manually
in three different places to get rid of it.
And whilst this is of course certainly doable,
it's unnecessary repetition.
And that's something we can typically avoid
by using and embracing React components.