- [Maximilian] Building
web apps with React
is not just about composing
components together
and making sure that the
logic works correctly.
That arguably is the most important part,
where at least it's the
biggest reason for using React.
But building React apps is
also about styling those apps.
You wanna make sure that
your applications look good
and styling is also an important part
of building components.
And there are different techniques
for setting styles dynamically
and for styling components
such that other components
are not affected by a
specific component's styles.
Therefore in this module,
we will dive into how
you can set up styles
in a conditional or dynamic way.
So how you, for example,
can switch certain styles
based on some conditions.
For example, if a user
enters an invalid input
and you want to color the input field red,
something like that.
And then we'll dive into
two popular approaches
for scoping styles to components,
so for setting up styles
such that they only affect the component
and are not added as global styles.
We'll have a look at styled components,
which is a third-party
library, a very popular one,
which allows us to set
up pre-styled components
with their own scoped styles.
And we'll have a look at a
concept called CSS modules.
And you will learn what
these different approaches
are all about, how you do work with them,
and how you could add
them to your next project.
Now, to dive into styling,
we need a demo project,
and to mix things up I got
a brand new project here.
Now I already prepared this one for you.
It's a very simple
project as you can tell.
You can basically add course goals,
like learn React, and that
will be added to this list.
You can also delete items from
there by clicking on them.
And that's basically it.
This project uses only
things which I covered
over the last course sections.
And of course, you'll find
that project attached.
You can simply download it.
You'll find the entire
project folder there.
And then, once you downloaded it,
simply opened a terminal,
navigate into this project folder,
and to run NPM install.
This will install all
the third-party packages
which are required since
the attached folder
does not come with a node modules folder
because that would unnecessarily
bloat the attachment.
NPM install simply installs all packages
and recreates the node modules folder.
And thereafter you have this project here,
which you can start with NPM start
to start the development server
and play around with the project.
Of course also feel free to
dive into the source files
to see how this project is structured.
As I already said, this
project only uses features
which you already know, like useState
and the functions which
are bound to events.
And we're then, for example,
also outputting lists of data
dynamically by calling map.
So that's all something you already saw
and there is nothing new there.
This however will be our
starting project for this section
where we are now going
to dive into styling.
So definitely explored
the source code files.
So did you understand this project
and thereafter we're going to have a look
at the different styling
options React gives us.