At this point in the course
we already learned a lot about React,
though I will say there also is more left to be learned.
But everything we learned up to this point
was about React doing things
inside of our app, in the browser.
And of course, that is why we do use React.
That is its main job
but we also only worked with local data up to this point.
So we only played around with dummy data
which was always just managed and stored in the browser.
In this course section, we are going to dive
into how you may connect your React Application
to a backend, to a database.
Because of course, many applications
probably all applications need to fetch data
from a database or store some data in a database eventually.
No matter if we're talking about
users that need to be created
and stored and locked in, or if we're talking about products
that need to be loaded or anything like that.
And therefore this section
is about establishing such a connection.
And it is about Sending Http Requests
from inside our React App to a backend.
And specifically we are going to learn
how exactly React Apps do interact with Databases?
Because whilst it's simple, as you will learn
it will not necessarily work as you expect it to work.
You will learn how you can send Http Requests
and work with responses, which you get back.
And we're going to have a look at how we can handle Errors
and Loading States in our application.