[Maximilian Schwarzmüller] At this point in the course
we are capable of building basic React apps.
We learn a lot about some of the most important features
that are baked into React.
But there's one thing that's really missing
or that we haven't had a close to look at until now.
And that is how React actually works behind the scenes.
Now, I know that to some students, this is not interesting.
You might be one of them.
And generally that's of course fine.
You are using a library like React
so that you don't have to do all the heavy lifting
on your own.
However, it really helps to understand
how something works that you're using
to ensure that you are using it correctly.
And whilst I, of course, do teach you common practices
and best practices throughout this course,
it nonetheless is important for you to know the tool
so that you are able to make the right decisions
in the apps you are going to build.
So even if that's not super interesting to you,
I would strongly recommend that you don't skip this module
and at least go through the videos at a higher speed
if you're really not interested.
We'll also dive in some new features
which are related to the behind the scenes work.
So I would recommend that you at least watch
those lectures, though, they will, of course make more sense
if you watched the entire module.
So what's in this module then?
We'll have a look at how React works behind the scenes.
That does not mean that we're going to dive
into the source code,
it means that I will show you how React works
with your components,
how it updates those components,
how State is related to all of that.
We'll understand that React uses
something which is called the Virtual DOM
and we'll understand how that works,
and how it affects updates made to the real Dom
which is in the end what drives your website in the browser.
And we'll take a closer look at state management,
how React does that.
And how a State updates are managed by React.
A lot of important concepts.
So let's dive right in.