At this point in the course,
you already learned a lot about some crucial core
React concepts, and of course,
you're going to learn even more
throughout the rest of this course.
But before you go there,
before you dive deeper into React, I strongly recommend
that you first practice what you learned
and that's exactly what this core section will be there for.
In this core section,
we're going to build two demo projects,
two basic yet non-trivial demo projects,
which allow you to apply your knowledge
and to practice what you learned.
Because in both projects you'll need to work
with components, state, some styling
and all these crucial core concepts we explored
throughout the previous sections.
Therefore, in this section here,
you'll practice how to split an existing component
and an existing application into multiple components,
and you'll also practice how to build
an application from scratch.
You will practice how to work with state,
how to manage and use state,
and you'll practice outputting list and conditional content.
Now, for both practice projects
which I prepared for you for this section here,
I will give you an introduction to those projects.
I'll provide you with some starting code
and I'll give you some tasks
or show you how the finished project should look like,
but I then absolutely would recommend
that you first try solving these tasks
and building those projects on your own
before you then take a look at my example solution,
which I of course will also provide as part of this section.
Because by trying these things on your own first,
you'll of course learn more about React
and you'll be able to confirm that you really understood
all these core concepts up to this point.
That being said, after every demo project introduction,
I will provide you with detailed solution steps
allowing you to compare your solution to mine,
and of course, whilst building that solution together
with you, I'll also explain why I chose a certain approach
and why I solved the tasks as I did solve them.
So definitely take a look at my solution as well,
but also definitely try those projects on your own first.