- [Instructor] We learned a lot about
some of the most important
features of React,
also about its core pillars
and how you style React apps.
Now, when you're building apps with React,
or in general, if you're
working as a developer,
you will encounter errors,
that will always happen,
you'll never write code
that is error free.
During your development process,
you will always face errors.
And in this module, you will
learn how to debug React apps.
So how you can find and fix errors,
because that's one of
the most important things
you need to be able to do as a developer,
it's often overlooked and I
see way too many developers
or all the students in my courses
that simply ask immediately
that they get an error,
they immediately look
for others to help them
and that's the wrong approach,
you need to be able to find
and solve errors on your own
because errors will always
be a part of development.
Therefore in this module,
we will explore how you can
make sense of the error messages
React froze at you in
certain circumstances,
we will learn how we can debug
and analyze React apps in general,
how we can understand our
code whilst it's executing,
and we'll explore the React Dev Tools,
an extra extension we can
install in the browser
to get a better React
developer experience.