Hi, and welcome to this course!
My name is Maximilian Schwarzmueller
and I will be your instructor
in this course where I will teach you
React from the ground
up, step by step, and in great depth!
In this first course section here,
I'll get you started with this course,
and get some organizational things
out of the way -
what you should know about React
and this course - and thereafter,
after an optional JavaScript
refresher section,
which you can take if it's been some time
since you last worked with JavaScript,
we're going to dive right in and explore
React in great detail.
And speaking of that, let's start
with the most
important question: What exactly is React?