Maximilian: Now, that we learned
about some important basics of React,
most importantly, about components and props
It's time to take the next step.
And in this course section, we're going to take
a closer look at user interaction and handling user events
like clicks or input into text fields and so on.
And we're going to have a look at the very important concept
of state in React apps because, you might remember,
that I mentioned earlier in the course
that with React we follow that declarative approach
where we, in the end, define desired target states
and React then takes care about reaching that state.
Well, that is correct and that is already
something we're using but, at the moment,
in the application we built thus far
and with the knowledge we gained, up to this point,
we can only build static applications
where the state never changes,
where we always output exactly the same.
And that's typically not what you want.
You want to have applications which are interactive,
so that you can React to clicks by the user
and to data being entered by the user
and which are reactive so that the application
also changes when certain things happen.
And, therefore, in this course module
we are going to take a look at handling events,
handling user events, like clicks and so on.
And we'll see how that works in React apps,
how we can add such event handlers and more.
And then, we're going to take a look at how we can ensure
that what's visible on the screen changes,
that we reach a different target state.
And for that, we're going to take a closer look
at this state concept in React
and we'll learn how we can manipulate the state
and transition from state A to state B, if we want to.
And, in general, in this section
we're going to learn about a couple of key concepts.
This is a section you absolutely should not skip.
And we're also going to take a closer look
at components and state again.
So, this is another fundamental section covering
core features of React, so let's dive in.