Now with the core basics and the foundation
about React and its most important features out of the way
and applied to our course project,
we're gonna take the next step in this module.
We're gonna have a look at three very important concepts
which you need to know as a React developer
and that will be effects, reducers and context.
Now these features are a little bit more advanced
which does not mean that they're difficult.
This just means you need know the other concepts first
which is why we are now diving into those concepts here
and with those features,
you will be able to make a huge step forward
towards more complex React applications.
Now in this module we will therefore take a closer look
at what effects are and how you can work
with so-called side effects which is what effects means,
but more on that in a second.
We'll have a look at how we can manage more complex state
in our components with reducers
and we will explore app-wide
or at least component-wide state so states that affect
multiple components with a concept called context
which is built into React to make sharing
state and state updates across components easier.
A lot of important features that are included here
so let's not waste any time and let's dive right in.