[Maximilian Schwarzmüller] As you can probably
tell by now we are diving deeper and deeper into React.
And in this module, we're going to have a look
at another core concept, which you will use
in a lot of React apps you're going to build
and that will be Custom Hooks
and how you can build your own Custom Hooks.
Now, up to this point in this course
we already worked a lot with Hooks,
with the built in React Hooks React offers
to us like useState, UseReducer, UseEffect
UseContext and so on.
So all these special React functions that start with Use.
You might remember that when I talked
about the rules of Hooks, I mentioned that
you can only use React Hooks
in React Component Functions and in Custom Hooks.
And I told you that those would be covered later.
Well, now is later.
Now we're going to explore how you can build your own Hooks,
why you might want to do that,
How exactly you do that, of course,
And we're going to do that
as a concrete example or multiple examples.
And we're also going to learn about the rules
and practices and best practices that apply when
you build your own Custom Hooks.