Over the last course sections,
the learning curve got a bit steeper
and we had a look
at more advanced yet crucial react concepts.
Especially of course, when we had a look at react hooks
like use effect, use context and also use reducer.
Therefore, before we dive deeper
into react, this course section is there
for you to practice what you learned together
with me by building another course project,
the Food Order app.
Now, of course we have demos in all course sections
but this is another slightly bigger application,
where all the key things you learned
throughout the last course sections again, come together
and can be seen in the context of a bigger project.
And of course, we're not just going to have a look
at those concepts covered in the last section,
but we will again see all core react features
in action, including components, state, and much more.
Now this is the application we are going to build.
It's a simple dummy food order app
where we got a list of meals from which we can choose.
And we can then add these meals to the cart,
also changed their amounts and also add them multiple times.
And of course we can also view the carts to see what's
in the cart here.
We can also change our cart from that page if we want to.
And ultimately we can, of course also click order, though
for the moment that won't do anything.
Instead, it will just add a little output here
in the console,
but we will, of course also have a closer look
at how we can store data in a database
or do other things with that later in the course.
But for the moment, this application is there
to practice all those key features we had a look
at over the last course sections.
Now, if you feel like it, you can
of course also try this on your own.
Attached to this lecture,
you find all the CSS files I plan to use
throughout this section,
and these file names also give you an idea
of which components I plan to use,
but this is totally optional.
It is a nice practice, but it will also be a big challenge.
Therefore it might definitely be worth a try,
but we can also simply walk through all
of that together,
to again practice all
these key concepts step-by-step together,
to make sure that after
this course section everything we learned up
to this point is super clear.