- [Instructor] By now we
know how to build components
and work with multiple components,
and we know how to work with state
and how to handle user events.
In this course section,
we're now going to dive
into rendering lists
and rendering conditional content.
So we'll have a look at how
we can output arrays of data
on our page and how we
can show different content
based on different conditions,
and that's exactly what we're going
to dive into in this module.
We're going to continue
working on the application
we already started over
the last course sections,
but in this module we're
now going to finish it
by adding these features.